[
    {
        "front": "font families",
        "back": "<p><strong>Serif</strong> - proportional and have serifs serifs are the decorations on the ends of the storkes</p><p><strong>Sans-Serif</strong> - proportional and do not have serifs</p><p><strong>Monospace</strong> - not proportional</p><p><strong>Cursive</strong> - attempt to emulate human handwriting</p><p><strong>Fancy</strong> - non really defined by any single characteristic other than our inability to classify them into the other font families</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "using generic font families",
        "back": "<p>body { font-family: sans-serif;}</p><p>h1,h2,h3,h4 { font-family: serif; }</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "specifying a Font Family",
        "back": "<p>h1 { font-family: TimesNR, serif; }</p><p>h2 { font-family: &#39;New Century Schoolbook&#39;, Times, serif; }</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "font-weight",
        "back": "b { font-weight: bold; }"
    },
    {
        "front": "font-size",
        "back": "<p>absolute sizes:</p><p>p.one { font-size: small; }</p><p>p.two { font-size: large; }</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>relative sizes (relative to parent):</p><p>p { font-size: medium; }</p><p>strong { font-size: larger; }</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "font size and inheritance",
        "back": "computed values are inherited in CSS not percentages  percentages are cumulative<p>computed values are inherited in CSS not percentages</p><p>percentages are cumulative</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "font-style",
        "back": "<p>p { font-style: normal; }</p><p>em { font-style: italic; }</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "font-variant",
        "back": "h1 { font-variant: small-caps; }"
    },
    {
        "front": "font-stretch",
        "back": "strong { font-stretch: wider; }"
    },
    {
        "front": "font-size-adjust",
        "back": "p {font: 10px Verdana, sans-serif; font-size-adjust: 0.58; }"
    },
    {
        "front": "font",
        "back": "<p>h1 {font: italic 900 small-caps 30px Verdana, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;}</p><p>h2 {font: bold normal italic 24px Verdana, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;}</p>"
    }
]
